Guide to the Richard Marshall Collection of Gay Erotica and Pornography MSS.498
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Magazines and Serials, 1948-2011, undated; 8 Linear Feet in 8 record cartons.
  - Subseries II.A. Magazines, 1948-2011, undated; 6.25 Linear Feet in 6 record cartons and 2 flat file folders.
    This subseries contains widely-themed magazines including clothing store quarterlies, fashion, sexual fetishes and interests, as well as pictoral pornographic publications.
    - A&F Quarterly, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, Christmas 1997, Issue 97 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A&F Quarterly, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, Spring 1998, Issue 98 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - A&F Quarterly, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, Summer 1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - A&F Quarterly, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, Fall, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - A&F Quarterly, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, 2002, Christmas, issue 22 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, Nov 1998, Christmas (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, Feb 1999, Spring Break (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Abercrombie &; Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, April 1999, Summer (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, July 1999, Back to School (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, Nov 1999, Christmas (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, Feb 2000, Spring Break (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, April 2000, Summer (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, July 2000, Back to School (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, July 2001, Back to School (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Maryland, Abercrombie & Fitch, July 2002, Back to School (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch, Ohio, Abercrombie & Fitch, Nov 2002, Christmas (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - AMG Raw, California, Golden State News, 1979, Issue 1 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Balls, California, Pantheon Productions, 1981, Issue 1 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Bel Ami, New York, Mandate Publications, 1996, v.3 n.3 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Black Sheets, California, Black Boots, 1997, nos.10 and 12 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1986, n.1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1986, n.1 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1987, n.2 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1987, n.3 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1987, n.4 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1988, n.5 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brown Hanky Journal - Guard Duty, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1989, n.6 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brown Hanky Journal - Guard Duty, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1989, n.6 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1990, n.7 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1991, n.8 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1993, n.9 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1995, n.10 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1995, n.11 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1996, n.12 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1997, n.13 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1998, n.14 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Brown Hanky Journal, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1998, n.15 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Brown Hanky Journal - Root 66 Scatman, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 2000, n.16 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Blue Boy's 10 Best Men, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Brentwood, v.3, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Brentwood,v.6, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Buddy, n.132, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Summer 2004, n.10 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Spring 2006, n.15 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Autumn 2006, n.17 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Spring 2007, n.19 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Summer 2007, n.20 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Autumn/Winter 2007, n.21 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Spring 2008, n.22 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Winter 2008/9, n.25, 2008-2009 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Spring 2009, n.26 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Fall 2009, n.27 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Butt, Amsterdam, Spring 2010, n.28 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Calvin Klein Jeans, Calvin Klein, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Colt: Anniversary Albums, California, Colt Studio, v.4, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Colt Men, California, Colt Studio, n.3, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Colt Men, California, Colt Studio, n.8, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Colt: The Men, The Myth, The Muscles (Collectors edition), California, Colt Studio, Winter, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1986, n.1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1986, n.8 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1987, n.9 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1987, n.10 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1987, n.11 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1989, n.12 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Colt Studio Presents, California, Colt Studio, 1998, n.19 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Crisc-oh, California, Incognito Publishing, n.1, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Cuir, California, The Leather Journal, 1995, Issue 17 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Cum and Get It, California, Academy Press, 1985, v.1 n.1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Cum Buddies, n.1, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1978, v.3 n.22 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1978, v.3 n.25 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1978, v.4 n.28 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1979, v.4 n.29 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1979, v.4 n.31 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1979, v.4 n.32 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1980, v.4 n.33 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1980, v.4 n.35 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1980, v.4 n.37 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1980, v.5 n.38 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1981, v.5 n.46 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1981, v.5 n.50 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Alternate Publishing, 1982, v.6 n.53 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer: The Leather Fraternity Class of '82, California, Alternate Publishing, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, v.10, n.87, Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Oct 1986, v.11 n.99 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Oct 1987, n.110 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Mar 1988, n.114 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, July 1988, n.119 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Aug 1988, n.120 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, May 1990, n.139 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Nov 1990, n.144 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, May 1991, n.149 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Oct 1993, n.168 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, July 1994, n.176 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Aug 1984, n.177, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Feb 1995, n.182 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Sept 1995, n.188 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Aug 1996, n.198 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Oct 1996, n.200 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Jan 1997, n.201 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Apr 1997, n.203 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, July 1997, n.205 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Drummer, California, Desmodus Inc, Aug 1997, n.207 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Drummer Buddies, California, Desmodus Inc, v.3., n.3, Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Drummer: Hard Core, California, Desmodus Inc, n.1, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Etienne: The Art of Etienne, Target Studios, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Etienne: The Erotic Art of Etienne, California, Falcon Studios, n.2, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Etienne: Storytime 5, Falcon Studios, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Etienne: Erotica, Book 1, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Eyemazing magazine, Amsterdam, Issue 4, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - The Fantastic World of Bill Ward, California, Alternate Publishing, v.3, Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Fizeek Art Quarterly, Washington D.C., Fizeek Enterprises, Fall 1966, n.19 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Fizeek Art Quarterly, Washington D.C., Fizeek Enterprises, Winter 1966, n.20 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Fizeek Art Quarterly, Washington D.C., Fizeek Enterprises, n.22, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Fizeek Art Quarterly, Washington D.C., Fizeek Enterprises, Spring 1968, n.23 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Folsom, California, Folsom Magazine, n.4, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Gai Pied Hebdo, n.5, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Gai Pied Hebdo, Paris, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Hand Book, California, 2007, v.1 Issue 4 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Hard Ball, Winter, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Hard Ball, Summer, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Heavy Load, Issue 2, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Him, London, Alan Purcell, Issue 2, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Hombre, California, Seven Seventy, v.1 n.1, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, April 1978, v.1 n.1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Sept 1978, v.1 n.5 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, 27363, v.1 n.8, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Dec 1978, v.2 n.16, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Aug 1979, v.2 n.20 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Oct 1980, v.3 n.5 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Feb 1981, v.3 n.8 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Oct 1981, v.4 n.15 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Dec 1981, v.4 n.16 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Feb 1982, v.4 n.19 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Jan 1991, v.14 n.1 (Box 8, Folder 8a)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Nov 1992, v.15 n.11 (Box 8, Folder 8a)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, Feb 1994, v.17 n.2 (Box 8, Folder 8a)
    - Honcho, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, April 1994, v.17 n.4 (Box 8, Folder 8a)
    - The Best of Honcho, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - The Best of Honcho: part two, New York, Modernismo Publications Ltd, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Illico, Paris, Illico Publications, Dec., 2003 (Box 8, Folder 9a)
    - In Magazine, Paris, June/July 1974, n.11, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Instigator Magazine, Instigator Magazine, nv.1 issue 5, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Instigator Magazine, California, Instigator Magazine, v.1 issue 6, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Instigator Magazine, California, Instigator Magazine, Issue 15, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - International Nudist Sun: Youth at Play, n.1, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Issue, New York, Issue Inc, Fall 2003, Issue 7 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Javelin, New York, Target Studios, n.1, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Javelin, Target Studios, n.3, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Jock Collectors Edition, New York, G. T. Publishing, v.1 n.2, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Jocks, California, Jocks Athletics Company, n.1, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Kaiserin, Luxembourg, Kaiserin, Sept 2009, Issue 3 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Kink, Barcelona, 2009, v.1 Issue 10 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - The Leather Journal, December 2003, Issue 165 (Box 8, Folder 18a)
    - Like It? Lick It!, Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Little Joe, Little Joe Magazine, n.2, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 19a)
    - Luger (Premier Collector's Edition), Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Macho, California, Alternate Publishing, 1980, v.1 n.4 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Alternate Publishing, 1983, v.2 n.6 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Desmodus Inc, Sept 1990, n.21 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Desmodus Inc, July 1993, n.29 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Desmodus Inc, Oct 1993, n.30 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Desmodus Inc, Feb 1994, n.31 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Desmodus Inc, July 1994, n.33 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, March 1997, n.35 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Macho, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, July 2000, n.46 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Mandate, New York, Mandate Publications, January 1997, v.21 n.1 (Box 8, Folder 21a)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1987, Issue 2 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1992, Issue 16 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1994, Issue 23 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1996, Issue 28 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1996, Issue 29 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1997, Issue 32 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manifest Reader, California, Alternate Publishing, 1999, Issue 39 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Manhood Rituals, California, Alternate Publishing, n.1, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Manhood Rituals, California, Alternate Publishing, n.6, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Manpower, California, Colt Studios, 1974, n.7 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Nous les hommes, Paris, Spring 1973, n.13 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Olympus, California, Colt Studio, v.1 n.5, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Olympus, California, Colt Studio, Issue 14, Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - On Campus, Falcon Studios, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - The One-Handed Library Brochure, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - The Longhorn Drive, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - A Trucker's Tale, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - The S & M Brothers, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - Satan's Nephew, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series: The Confessions of Satan's Nephew, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series: The Secret DIary of Uncle Joe, Florida, D&W Enterprises (Reprinted from 1978), 1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - El Toro: The Fugitive Master, Florida, D&W Enterprises, Also Brown Hanky Journal n.3.5, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - The Return of the Coney Island Knights, Florida, D&W Enterprises, Also Brown Hanky Journal n.8.5, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - Overtime Parking, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - The West Side Highway Story, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - Adventures at Roadside Park, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - Adventures at Roadside Park, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - My Adventures at Glory Hole Lodge, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - The One-Handed Reader Series - Ardmore Station, Florida, D&W Enterprises, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Perry Ellis Advertising Campaign Book, Perry Ellis, Spring, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Perry Ellis America Advertising Campaign Book. Perry Ellis, Spring, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Powerplay, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, 1991, v.1 Issue 1 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Powerplay, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, 1992, v.1 issue 3 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Powerplay, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, May 1995, Issue 6 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Powerplay, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, May 1996, Issue 10 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Powerplay, California, Brush Creek Media Inc, Dec 1996, Issue 12 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, April 1997, n.18 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, June 1997, n.20 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Oct 1998, n.34 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Nov/Dec 1998, n.35 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Jan 1999, n.36 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Feb 1999, n.37 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, May 1999, n.40 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, June/July 1999, n.41 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Aug 1999, n.42 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Sept 1999, n.43 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Oct 1999, n.44 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Nov 1999, n.45 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Dec 1999, n.46 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Jan 2000, n.47 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Feb 2000, n.48 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, March 2000, n.49 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project X, Paris, PX Presse, Apr 2000, n.50 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, April 1999, v.14 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, July/Aug 1999, v.17 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, Nov 1999, v.20 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, Dec 1999, v.21 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, Jan 2000, v.22 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, Feb 2000, v.23 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, March 2000, v.25 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, Apr 2000, v.25 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Project X: Agenda, Paris, PX Presse, May 2000, v.26 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Provocateur, California, Alluvial Publishing, Dec 1995, v.1 issue 2 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Provocateur, California, Alluvial Publishing, Feb 1996, v.1 issue 3 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Provocateur, California, Alluvial Publishing, July 1996, v.2 issue 5 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Provocateur, California, Alluvial Publishing, Oct 1996, v.2 issue 1 (Box 9, Folder 14a)
    - Provocateur, California, Alluvial Publishing, March 1997, v.2 issue 2 (Box 9, Folder 14a)
    - R.F.M.: Three Bulls in Debauchery. R.F. M., California, R. F. M. Products, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - R.F.M.: The Life of a Masochist, California, R. F. M. Products, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - R.F.M.: Three Bulls Meet The Rubbermaster, California, R. F. M. Products, 1981 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Ramrod, New York, Target Studios, n.1, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Ramrod, New York, Target Studios, n.1, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Ramrod, New York, Target Studios, n.2, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - The Rawhide Male, Illinois, Checkmate Guild Ltd, n.3, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - The Rawhide Male, Illinois, Checkmate Guild Ltd, n.4, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Scat, Oct 1994, Issue 22 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Scat, Oct 1995, Issue 25 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Skin, Delaware, Quality Publishing Inc, n.2, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Skin, Delaware, Quality Publishing Inc, v.4 n.3, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Skin, Delaware, Quality Publishing Inc, n.4, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Skin, Delaware, Quality Publishing Inc, n.5, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Solo Sleaze, California, Arena Publications, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Spezial Fotografie (Bruce Weber: Roadside America), No. 22, 2000 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Spurs, California, Colt Studio, 1984, n.10 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Spurs, California, Colt Studio, 1993, n.20 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Spurs, California, Colt Studio, 1993, n.21 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - The Sphincterian Quarterly, Virginia, David Barton-Jay Projects, Fall 1994, Issue 1 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - The Sphincterian Quarterly, Virginia, David Barton-Jay Projects, Summer 1995, Issue 4 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - The Sphincterian Quarterly, Virginia, David Barton-Jay Projects, Winter 1995, Issue 5 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Stallion, New York, Stallion Publications, Aug 1990, v.3 n.6 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Steam, California, PDA Press, Spring 1993, v.1 issue 1 (Box 10, Folder 6a)
    - Steam, California, PDA Press, Spring 1994, v.2 issue 1 (Box 10, Folder 6a)
    - Steam, California, PDA Press, Autumn 1994, v.2 issue 3 (Box 10, Folder 6a)
    - Steam, California, PDA Press, Winter 1994, v.2 issue 4 (Box 10, Folder 6a)
    - Steam, California, PDA Press, Spring 1995, v.3 issue 1 (Box 10, Folder 6a)
    - Steam, California, PDA Press, Summer 1995, v.3 issue 2 (Box 10, Folder 6a)
    - Steam, California, PDA Press, Autumn 1995, v.3 issue 3 (Box 10, Folder 6a)
    - Strength and Health, Pennsylvania, Strength and Health Publishing Company, Nov., 1948 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1981, v.1 n.1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1981, v.1 n.2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1982, v.1 n.3 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1982, v.2 n.1 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1982, v.2 n.2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1983, v.2 n.3 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1983, v.3 n.1 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1983, v.3 n.2 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1983, v.3 n.3 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1984, v.3 n.4 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1984, v.3 n.5 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1984, v.3 n.6 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1984, v.4 n.1 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1984, v.4 n.2 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1984, v.4 n.3 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1985, v.4 n.4 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1985, v.4 n.5 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1985, v.4 n.6 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1985, v.5 n.2 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1986, v.5 n.4 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1986, v.5 n.5 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1986, v.6 n.1 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1986, v.6 n.2 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1987, v.6 n.4 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1987, v.6 n.5 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1987, v.6 n.6 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1987, v.7 n.1 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1987, v.7 n.2 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1988, v.7 n.3 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1988, v.7 n.4 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Stroke, Stroke, 1988, v.7 n.5 (Box 10, Folder 13)